Guide to the New Yorkers at Work Oral History Collection OH.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
New Yorkers at Work Oral History Collection
1979-2000
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Bernhardt, Debra E.
Baskin, Alex
Harris, Joseph
Kornblun, Joyce
Ramirez, Antonio
Weinstock, Louis, 1903-1994
OH.001
15 Linear Feet (approximately 300 cassette tapes)
New Yorkers at Work is an ongoing oral history project of New York University's Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives that seeks to document the history of labor and the working experiences of New Yorkers.
Access Restrictions
Some restrictions on access. For information contact: tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection was created by Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives with funding from the Rockefeller Foundation; additional materials were donated by Alex Baskin in 1997, Joseph Harris in 1991, Joyce Kornblun in 1982, Antonio Ramirez in 1996, and Louis Weinstock in 1981. The accession numbe associated with this collection is 1979.012.
Arrangement
The interviews are grouped into 1 series, arranged alphabetically by the name of the interviewee in finding aid. Access compact disks have been assigned numbers based on order of digitization.
Historical/Biographical Note
Begun in 1979, The New Yorkers at Work Oral History Collection is an ongoing series of interviews, conducted primarily by the staff of New York University's Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, that document the history of labor in the metropolitan area. The largest group of interviews were collected for the New Yorkers at Work: Oral Histories of Life, Labor, and Industry Curriculum Project. In 1980, with a grant from the New York Council for the Humanities, about 150 interviews were conducted with workers and union activists in industries representative of the city's economy. Eight documentary radio programs were produced from these interviews for broadcast over National Public Radio. Additional interviews were conducted by Archive staff to augment archival and manuscript collections; a few others were donated by researchers or students. The most extensive of these was a series of 15 interviews conducted by SUNY Old Westbury Labor Studies students of Professor Joe Harris—many of them with Long Island labor leaders.
Scope and Content Note
The collection consists of oral history interviews broadly representative of 20th century New York City working conditions and union experiences. Topics include the impact of labor-saving construction techniques on the building trades; immigrant labor; CIO organization; the role of the Left in the labor movement and the impact of the expulsion of communist-dominated unions in 1949; public employee collective bargaining and the Fiscal Crisis of 1974-75; clerical organizing; new technology and its impact on printers and longshoremen; and the quest for economic opportunity by minorities and women. Please note the use of some interviews is restricted; transcripts or indexes exist for several of the tapes/CDs.
Notable interviewees include: Harry Avrutin, Brenda Berkman, Peter J. Brennan, Philip A. Carey, Charles Cogen, Edward J. Cleary, Sam Dolgoff, Ralph Fasanella, Abram Flaxer, Harry Fleischman, Philoine Fried, Dolores Huerta, Theodore Woodrow Kheel, Kitty Krupat, Josie McMillian, Joyce Miller, Pauline Newman, Lillian Roberts, Cleveland L. Robinson, Joe Stack, Leon Sverdlove, and Belle Zeller.
Labor unions and other organizations documented include: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; New York Joint Board; AFSCME; District Council 37 (New York, N.Y.); Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union of America; Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.); Communist Party of the United States of America; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers; Local no. 3 (New York, N.Y.), International Jewelry Workers Union; International Ladies' Garmet Workers' Union; International Longshoremen's Association; National Maritime Union of America; New York Hotel Trades Council; Newspaper Guild of New York; Social Service Employees Union; Local 371 (New York, N.Y.); United Automobile; Aircraft, and Vehicle Workers of America; District 65; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America; United Farm Workers of America; United Federation of Teachers; United Office and Professional Workers of America; United Storeworkers (Organization); and Local 3 (New York, N.Y.).
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Access to audiovisual materials in this collection is available through digitized access copies. Researchers may view an item's original container, but the media themselves are not available for playback because of preservation concerns. Materials that have already been digitized are noted in the collection's finding aid and can be requested in our reading room. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Labor unions -- Organizing -- United States.; Oral histories (literary works); Construction workers -- New York (State) -- New York -- Interviews; Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York -- History -- 20th century.; Electric industry workers |z New York (State) |z New York |v Interviews.; Merchant mariners |z New York (State) |z New York |v Interviews.; Clerks |z New York (State) |z New York |v Interviews.; Hotels |x Employees |z New York (State) |z New York |v Interviews.; Clothing workers -- New York (State) -- New York -- Interviews.; Women employees -- New York (State) -- New York -- Interviews.; Municipal officials and employees |z New York (State) |z New York |v Interviews.; Stevedores -- New York (State) -- New York -- Interviews.; Working class -- New York (State) -- New York -- Interviews.; United Storeworkers (Organization). Local 3 (New York, N.Y.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. New York Joint Board; Avrutin, Harry; Stack, Joe -- Interviews.; Sverdlove, Leon -- Interviews.; Robinson, Cleveland L. (Cleveland Lowellyn), 1914-1995; Miller, Joyce -- Interviews.; Newman, Pauline.; Huerta, Dolores, 1930-; Fried, Philoine; Cleary, Edward J. (Edward John), 1906-; Dolgoff, Sam, 1902-1990 -- Interviews; Carey, Philip A.; Cogen, Charles, 1903- -- Interviews; Zeller, Belle, 1903-; Brennan, Peter J., 1918-1996; Berkman, Brenda -- Interviews; Fleischman, Harry -- Interviews; Flaxer, Abram, 1904- -- Interviews; Kheel, Theodore Woodrow -- Interviews; Fasanella, Ralph -- Interviews; Krupat, Kitty; McMillian, Josie -- Interviews.; Roberts, Lillian; United Federation of Teachers; AFSCME. District Council 37 (New York, N.Y.); United Office and Professional Workers of America; International Longshoremen's Association; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America; United Farm Workers of America; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. District 65; New York Hotel Trades Council; Social Service Employees Union. Local 371; Newspaper Guild of New York; National Maritime Union of America; International Jewelry Workers Union; Communist Party of the United States of America; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers. Local 3 (New York, N.Y.); Bakery, Confectionery, and Tobacco Workers International Union; Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.); Baskin, Alex; Harris, Joseph; Kornblun, Joyce; Ramirez, Antonio; Weinstock, Louis, 1903-1994
- Bernard and Marty Adelstein, undated; cuid264 (Cd OH-01-001 / OH-01-002, Cassette 182A - 182B)
  General
  Transcript available Box 1
- Marge Albert, undated (Cassette 1A - 1O)
  General note
  Index available
- Tony Alleyne, Nov 21, 1981 (Cassette 2A, Cd OH-01-005)
  Index available; Transcript available Box 1
- Joseph Alissipi, Apr 15, 1990 (Cassette 209A - 209C, Cd OH-01-431 / OH-01-432 / OH-01-433)
  Transcript available Box 1; Index available; Release form
- Kathy Andrade, Dec 11, 1998 (Cassette 251A - 251C)
- Sam Angel, Jan 3, 1980 (Cd OH-01-196, Cassette 3A)
  Transcript available Box 1; Release form Yes
- Stanley Aslanian, Jul 11, 1984 (Cd OH-01-006, Cassette 137A)
- Sylvia & George Aronov, Dec 12, 1995 - Dec 20, 1995 (Cd OH-01-197 / OH-01-198 / OH-01-199 / OH-01-200, Cd OH-01-201 / OH-01-202 / OH-01-203 / OH-01-204, Cd OH-01-205 / OH-01-206, Cassette 152A - 152E)
- Larry Atkins, Jul 16, 1996 (Cassette 232A - 232B, Cd OH-01-207)
  Transcript available Box 1; Index available; Release form Yes
- William Atkinson, Jun 16, 1981 (Cassette 4A, Cd OH-01-007 / OH-01-008)
  Electronic Transcript and Index available
  Release form Yes
- Harry Avrutin, Jul 7, 1981 (Cassette 5A, Cd OH-01-009)
- Irving Axelrod, Sep 18, 1980 (Cassette 6A - 6B, Cd OH-01-011, Cd OH-01-010 / OH-01-011)
- Gilbert Banks, Oct 22, 1980 (Cassette 7A - 7B, Cd OH-01-210 / OH-01-211)
- Roger Baldwin, undated (Cassette 156A - 156C, Cd OH-01-209)
  Electronic Transcript available
- Harry Belkin, Sep 18, 1980 (Cd OH-01-012 / OH-01-013, Cassette 8A - 8B)
- Jim Bell, undated (Cassette 9A, Cd OH-01-014)
- Peter Bell, Aug 29, 1981 (Cd OH-01-477 / OH-01-478, Cassette 10A - 10B)
- Ronald and Peter Bell, Aug 29, 1981 (Cassette 11A - 11B, Cd OH-01-015 / OH-01-016)
- Jane Benedict, Dec 6, 1983 (Cd OH-01-372, Cassette 14A)
- Gloria Bendhurst, undated (Cassette 12A, Cd OH-01-370 / OH-01-371)
- Julia Benicci, Sep 20, 1981 (Cd OH-01-224 / OH-01-225, Cassette 13A)
- Robert Benson, Apr 15, 1991 (Cd OH-01-017, Cassette 193A)
- Brenda Berkman, Apr 4, 1993; Mar 1, 1995 (Cassette 214A - 214C, Cd OH-01-212 / OH-01-213 / OH-01-214)
  Transcript available Box 1; Release form
- Al Berknopf, May 6, 1980 - May 8, 1980
- Howard Bethel, Apr 14, 1978 (Box 1, Item Session: 137)
- Jack Bigel, Jul 30, 1987 (Cd OH-01-215)
- Ted Bleeker, Mar 6, 1996 (Cassette 154, Cd OH-01-352 / OH-01-353 / OH-01-354)
  Transcript available Box 1; Release form Y
- John Boer, Feb 6, 1981; Mar 2, 1981 (Cd OH-01-216 / OH-01-217 / OH-01-218 / OH-01-219, Cd OH-01-220 / OH-01-221, Cassette 15A - 15C)
- Herbie Bostick, Jul 16, 1996 (Cassette 234A - 234B, Cd OH-01-373 / OH-01-374)
- August Brand, May 14, 1980 (Cassette 16A - 16B, Cd OH-01-023 / OH-01-024)
- Sara Bransford, Apr 12, 1990 (Cassette 180A - 180B, Cd OH-01-025 / OH-01-026 / OH-01-027)
- Peter Brennan, undated (Cassette 194A MISSING)
  Electronic Transcript available; Release form Yes
- George Brooks, Apr 8, 1991 (Cd OH-01-028, Cassette 195A)
- May Brooks, Dec 13, 1994 (Box 1, Item Session: 225)
  Electronic Transcript available; Release form Yes*amended
- Thomas R. Brooks, 1991 (Cd OH-01-492 / OH-01-029 / OH-01-030, Cassette 210A - 210B)
  General Note
- Frank Brown, Nov 25, 1980 (Cd OH-01-222 / OH-01-223, Cassette 17A - 17B)
- Mollie Brown, Apr 3 (Cassette 189A)
  No Transcript
- Al Berknopf, May 6, 1980; Oct 8, 1980 (Cassette 157A - 157B, Cd OH-01-020 / OH-01-021 / OH-01-022)
- Armando Betanses, Jul 23, 1996 (Cassette 233A - 233B, Cd OH-01-018 / OH-01-019)
- Bernard Cacchione, Jun 30, 1980; cuid265 (Cassette 18A, Cd Cd: OH-01-834)
- Lonnie Cacchione, undated (Cd OH-01-233 / OH-01-234, Cassette 19A)
  Transcript available Box 2; Index available
- Angus Campbell, Jul 19, 1980 (Cd OH-01-031, Cassette 20A)
  Transcript available Box 2
- Anthony Caprano, Jun 11, 1981 (Cassette 144A, Cd OH-01-032)
  Transcript available Box 2; Release form Yes
- Joe Califf, Apr 24, 1994 (Cassette 219A - 219B, Cd OH-01-235 / OH-01-236)
- Father Philip Carey, Feb 19, 1981 (Cassette 21A - 21C, Cd OH-01-434-436)
  Index available; Release form Yes
- Elizabeth Smith Cassidy, Dec 6, 1996 (Cassette 235A - 235B, Cd OH-01-033 / OH-01-034)
  Transcript available Box 2; Index available; Release form Yes
- Joseph E. Cavanagh, Dec 20, 1988 (Cassette 181A - 181B)
- Frank Cedarwall, undated (Cassette 151A - 151B, Cd OH-01-035 / OH-01-036)
- May Chen, Apr 4, 2003 (Cassette 259A, Cd OH-01-237)
  Related Archival Materials
  Additional transcript of this interview can be found in the Asian Garment Workers in New York City Oral History Collection (OH 018).
- Sam Cimaglia, Nov 17, 1990 (Cassette 171A - 171B, Cd OH-01-037 / OH-01-038)
- George Cirkiel, May 20, 1980 (Cassette 22A, Cd OH-01-238)
- Ed Cleary, Oct 9, 1980 (Cassette 24A - 24B)
- Ed Cleary Sr., Nov 30, 1980 (Cassette 23A MISSING)
- Victor Clement, Jul 3, 1980 (Cd OH-01-039 / OH-01-040, Cassette 25A - 25B)
- Cynthia Copeland Cochran, Jun 7, 1994 (Cd OH-01-241, Cassette 220A)
- Charles Cogen, Oct 15, 1980 (Cassette 26A - 26B, Cd OH-01-239 / OH-01-240)
- Charles Everett Colcord, Nov 23, 1984 (Cassette 27A - 27B, Cd OH-01-041 / OH-01-042 / OH-01-043)
- Roger Cole, undated (Box 1, Item no tape)
- Mabel Collie, Oct 12, 1990 (Cd OH-01-044, Cassette 173A)
- Sharon Collie, Oct 24, 1990 (Cassette 172A)
- Mary Condon, Nov 2, 1980 (Cassette 28A, Cd OH-01-045 / OH-01-046)
- Simm Covington, undated (Cassette 196A, Cd OH-01-242)
- Ed Cross, Mar 20, 1980 (Cassette 29A - 29B, Cd OH-01-047 / OH-01-048)
- George Culliman, Mar 26, 1981 (Cd OH-01-243 / OH-01-244 / OH-01-245 / OH-01-246 / OH-01-247 / OH-01-248, Cassette 30A - 30C)
- Bob Croghan, May 13 and May 20, 2004 (Dvd OH-01-489 / OH-01-490)
  Beta File; Access DVD
- Armand D'Angelo, Jul 22, 1986 (Cassette 146A, Cd OH-01-436 / OH-01-437)
- Frank DaVito, Aug 28, 1989 (Cassette 166A, Cd OH-01-049)
- Louis D'Incecco, undated (Cassette 183A, Cd OH-01-249)
- Domenic DiPaola, Jan 13, 1994 (Cd OH-01-050 / OH-01-051, Cassette 218A - 218B)
- Robert Dobbs, undated (Cassette 246A)
- Herbert Dohms, Jun 2, 1990 (Cd OH-01-052, Cassette 167A)
- Esther Dolgoff, Apr 17, 1979 (Cassette 186A, Cd OH-01-053)
- Sam Dolgoff, Jul 21, 1981 (Cassette 31A, Cd OH-01-054 / OH-01-055)
- Julius Drumright, Jul 23, 1977 (Cd OH-01-056, Cassette 32A)
  Index available; Release form yes
- Johnnie Dwyer, Nov 21, 1980 (Cd OH-01-057 / OH-01-058, Cassette 34A - 34B)
  Electronic Transcript available; Release form
- Jeff Eichler, Mar 8, 1994; cuid36291 (Cassette 225A - 225B, Cd OH-01-250 / OH-01-251)
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Duration: 96 minutes; digitized recording is in two parts, part "A" (32 minutes) and part "B" (64 minutes).
- Emmanuel Eisenhandler, undated (Cassette 184A)
- Hilliard Ellis African-American trade unionism; UAW/Transport Workers, 1981 (Cd OH-01-252 / OH-01-253, Cassette 35A)
- Ralph Fasenella, Apr 6, 1981 (Cassette 36A, Cd OH-01-059 / OH-01-060)
- Charles Fay, Apr 10, 1986 (Cd OH-01-061 / OH-01-062, Cassette 37A - 37B)
- Al Filardo, Oct 10, 1986 (Cd OH-01-063 / OH-01-064, Cassette 38A - 38B)
- Ann Filardo, undated (Cassette 197A-B, Cd OH-01-438 / OH-01-439 / OH-01-440)
- Jack Finn, Jul 22, 1981 (Cd OH-01-367 / OH-01-368 / OH-01-369, Cassette 39A - 39C)
- Father Joseph Fitzpatrick, Oct 12, 1990 (Cassette 169A - 169D)
- Abe Flaxer, Apr 7, 1981; Apr 23, 1981; May 18, 1981 (Cassette 40A - 40D, Cd OH-01-485 / OH-01-486)
- Harry Fleischman, Jun 8, 1981; Jun 15, 1981; Jun 22, 1981 (Cassette 41A - 41D, Cd OH-01-254 / OH-01-255 / OH-01-256 / OH-01-257 / OH-01-258 / OH-01-259)
- Henry Foner, Nov 21, 2002 (Cd OH-01-260 / OH-01-261, Cassette 247A)
  Transcript available Box 3; Release form Yes
- Henry Foner and Charles Klare, Jul 20, 1998 (Cd OH-01-262 / OH-01-263)
  Transcript available Box 3
- Maurice Fredericks, Apr 28, 1981; Jul 3, 1981 (Cassette 42A - 42D, Cd OH-01-441 / OH-01-442 / OH-01-443)
  Release form
- Daniel P. French, Oct 23, 1992 (Cassette 213A, Cd OH-01-065)
- Sam Friedman, Feb 19, 1986; Jan 21, 1990 (Cassette 165A, Cd OH-01-465, Cassette 43A - 43F)
- Allen Ernestine, Feb 4, 1985 (Cd OH-01-003 / OH-01-004, Cassette 162A - 162B)
- Philoene Fried, daughter of Sidney Hillman, Jan 12, 1988 (Cassette 150A - 150B, Cd OH-01-066, Cd OH-01-067)
  Transcript available Box 4; Release form Yes
- Jimi Gavin National Maritime Union, Aug 26, 1986; Aug 29, 1986 (Cassette 163A - 163F, Cd OH-01-068 / OH-01-069 / OH-01-070 / OH-01-071 / OH-01-072, Cd OH-01-073 / OH-01-074 / OH-01-075 / OH-01-076 / OH-01-077 / OH-01-078)
- James Garry, Mar 21, 1989 (Cassette 221A)
- Bessie Geller, Jun 29, 1991 (Cassette 191A MISSING)
- Irving Genn, Mar 29, 1990 (Cassette 164A - 164B, Cd OH-01-079 / OH-01-080)
- Laviere (Larry) Gentile, Sep 19, 1996 (Cd OH-01-081 / OH-01-082, Cassette 237A - 237B)
- Miriam Gittelson, Jun 3, 1999 (Cd OH-01-083 / OH-01-084, Cassette 255A - 255B)
- John Glasel, Jun 2, 1993 (Cassette 215A - 215B)
- Thomas Gleason, Jul 31, 1980 (Cassette 44A, Cd OH-01-085)
  Scope and Contents
  International Longshoremen's Association
- Max Goodheim, Jun 30, 1981; Sep 21, 1981 (Cassette 45A - 45C, Cd OH-01-264 / OH-01-265 / OH-01-266 / OH-01-267 / OH-01-268)
  Transcript available Box 3; Index available
- Michael Goodwin, May 28, 1999 (Cassette 252A, Cd OH-01-086)
- Lou Gordon, Sep 10, 1979 (Cd OH-01-269 / OH-01-270 / OH-01-271 / OH-01-272, Cassette 46A - 46B)
- Joseph Gould, Dec 2, 1989 (Cassette 158A - 158B, Cd OH-01-087 / OH-01-088)
- Paul Green, Sep 25, 1992 (Cassette 212A - 212B, Cd OH-01-273 / OH-01-274 / OH-01-275)
- Florence Grogan, Oct 25, 1996 (Cd OH-01-466 / OH-01-467, Cassette 236A)
  Transcript available Box 3; Index available; Release form Yes
- Paul Hall, 1969 (Cd OH-01-491, Cassette 47A)
- Helmut A. Hallex, Mar 8, 1980; Mar 22, 1980 (Cassette 48A - 48D, Cd OH-01-276 / OH-01-277 / OH-01-278 / OH-01-279 / OH-01-280 / OH-01-281)
- James Haughton, Oct 22, 1980 (Cassette 49A - 49B, Cd OH-01-089 / OH-01-090)
- Peter Hawley, Dec 6, 1983 (Cd OH-01-392 / OH-01-393 / OH-01-394, Cassette 50A - 50B)
- Charles Hayes, Jul 23, 1981 (Cd OH-01-386, Cassette 51A)
- Stan Hill, Sep 6, 1982 (Cd OH-01-322, Cassette 52A)
- Harold Hoffman, Feb 14, 1985 (Cd OH-01-468, Cassette 161A)
- Walter Hooke, Jul 16, 1994 (Cassette 223A - 223D, Cd OH-01-375 / OH-01-376 / OH-01-377 / OH-01-378)
- Ben Holzman, May 17, 1981 (Cassette 53A MISSING)
- Dolores Huerta, Sep 4, 1986 (Cd OH-01-091, Cassette 54A)
- Sidney Jonas, Dec 12, 1982; Sep 12, 1983; Sep 3, 1983 (Cassette 55A - 55D, Cd OH-01-357 / OH-01-358 / OH-01-359 / OH-01-360)
- Julie, Nov 15, 1980 (Cassette 56A, Cd OH-01-479)
- Joe Kanowe, undated (Cd OH-01-284 / OH-01-285, Cd OH-01-285)
- Edna Kaplan, undated (Cassette 218.5 MISSING)
  Transcript available
- Harry Kelber, Jun 19, 1980 (Cassette 57A, Cd OH-01-469: OH-01-475)
- Ruth Kessler Taylor, undated (Cd OH-01-444 / OH-01-445 / OH-01-446 / OH-01-447 / OH-01-448 / OH-01-449, Cassette 121A-C)
  Transcript available Box 5; Release form Yes
- Theodore Kheel, undated (Cassette 58A, Cd OH-01-400)
- Ida Klaus, Mar 10, 1981 (Cassette 59A - 59B, Cd OH-01-379 / OH-01-380 / OH-01-381 / OH-01-382)
  Public Employment Relations Board; "Little Wagner Act"
- Jerome Klied, Jul 17, 1980 (Cassette 60A, Cd OH-01-286 / OH-01-287)
- Joe Knowles & John Hanbury, Sep 12, 1985 (Cd OH-01-092 / OH-01-093 / OH-01-094, Cassette 61A - 61B)
- Riki Kosut, Nov 10, 1980 (Cassette 63A, Cd OH-01-095 / OH-01-096)
- Sam Kovenetsky, Nov 6, 1979; Dec 19, 1979 (Cd OH-01-401 / OH-01-402, Cassette 64A - 64B)
- Kitty Krupat, undated (Cd OH-01-403 / OH-01-404, Cassette 65A - 65C)
- Israel Kugler, undated (Cassette 230A MISSING)
- Connie Kopelov, Jan 29, 1981 (Cassette 62A - 62B)
- Celia Langert, Jan 23, 1989 (Cassette 153A, Cd OH-01-480)
- Jesse Langston, Jul 17, 1982 (Cd OH-01-097 / OH-01-098, Cassette 66A)
- Anita Lathan, Sep 24, 1999 (Cassette 256A - 256B)
- Oliver Leeds, Aug 9, 1983 (Cassette 147A - 147C, Cd OH-01-288 / OH-01-289 / OH-01-290)
- Sarah Leichter, Apr 26, 1979; Jun 7, 1979; Jun 21, 1979 (Box 1, Item Session: 33)
- Sam & Bessie Levine, Oct 3, 1980 (Cd OH-01-099 / OH-01-100, Cassette 68A - 68B)
- Barry Lipton, Apr 2, 1997 (Cassette 238A - 238B, Cd OH-01-101 / OH-01-102 / OH-01-103)
- George Litsios, Jun 23, 1994 (Cassette 222A - 222C, Cd OH-01-291 / OH-01-292)
- David Livingston, Oct 25, 1979 (Cassette 69A - 69C, Cd OH-01-305 / OH-01-306 / OH-01-307)
- Ethel Loebman, undated (Cd OH-01-293)
- Cynthia Long, Oct 19, 1980 (Cd OH-01-108 / OH-01-109, Cassette 70A - 70B)
- Vincent Longhi, Dec 11, 1993 (Cassette 216A - 216B, Cd OH-01-294 / OH-01-295)
- John Lopez, Nov 10, 1990 (Cassette 175A, Cd OH-01-104 / OH-01-105)
- Louis Lufkowitz, May 21, 1981 (Cd OH-01-106 / OH-01-107, Cassette 67A)
  Release form Lufkowitz
- John P. Lundergan, Apr 9, 1991 (Cassette 199A)
- James Lustig, Jun 15, 1981 (Cd OH-01-110, Cassette 71A)
- Bill Lynch, undated (Cd OH-01-111, Cassette 72A)
- Robert MacGregor, Dec 21, 1988 (Cassette 179A - 179B)
- Sam Madell, Jul 16, 1980 (Cd OH-01-493 / OH-01-494 / OH-01-495, Cassette 73A - 73C)
- John Maguire, Jul 18, 1990 (Cassette 168A - 168B)
- Max Manes, Mar 2, 1989 (Cassette 154A - 154C)
- Julius Margolin, Jun, 15 2004 (Cd OH-01-112 / OH-01-113 / OH-01-114, Cassette 258A - 258B)
- Narciso Martas, Jun 25, 1996 (Cd OH-01-115 / OH-01-116, Cassette 239A)
  Transcript available Box 4; Index available; Release form Yes
- Anne B. Martin, Sep 12, 1995 (Cassette 156A-B, Cd OH-01-405 / OH-01-406 / OH-01-407)
- George Martin, undated (Cassette 200A)
- Jay Mazur, undated (Cd OH-01-117, Cassette 261A)
  A transcript of this interview can be found in the Asian Garment Workers in New York City Oral History Collection (OH 018).
- Moore McCormick, Jul 28, 1980 (Cassette 141A)
- George McDonald, Nov 29, 1994 (Cassette OH-01-450, Cassette 224A)
- Bob McElroy, Jul 14, 1980 (Cassette 74A - 74F)
- Bobbie McGee, Jul 20, 1981 (Cd OH-01-118 / OH-01-119, Cassette 75A)
- Bertha McGowan, Sep 1, 1981 (Cd OH-01-120 / OH-01-121, Cassette 143A)
- Brian McLaughlin, undated (Cd OH-01-451)
  Transcript available Box 4
- Josie McMillian, Jan 26, 1981 (Cassette 142A, Cd OH-01-122)
  Transcript available Box 4; Partial and Index available
- Joseph McPartlin, Apr 18, 1991 (Cassette 201A)
- Patricia Meckle, Sep 6, 1985 (Cd OH-01-408 / OH-01-409 / OH-01-410, Cassette 76A - 76C)
- George Meisler, Dec 12, 1979; Dec 21, 1979 (Cd OH-01-411 / OH-01-412 / OH-01-413 / OH-01-414, Cassette 77A - 77D)
- Susan Metz & Merry Tucker, Aug 25, 1981 (Cassette 125A MISSING)
- Marcella Loring Michelson, Jun 18, 1980 (Cassette 79A, Cd OH-01-123)
- Clarina Michelson, Oct 20, 1979 (Cassette 78A - 78B, Cd OH-01-296 / OH-01-297 / OH-01-298)
- William Michelson, Jan 15, 1981 (Cassette 80A, Cd OH-01-124)
- Geraldine Miller, Jun 18, 1981 (Cassette 81A, Cd OH-01-125 / OH-01-126)
- Joyce Miller, Jul 2, 1981 (Cd OH-01-361, Cassette 82A)
  Transcript available Box 4; Index available; Transcript available Box 4Release form Yes
- Saul Mills, Apr 3, 1981 (Cassette 83A - 83B, Cd OH-01-127 / OH-01-128 / OH-01-129)
- Eleanor Mishnun, Mar 22, 1985; May 3, 1985; May 22, 1985 (Cd OH-01-299 / OH-01-300 / OH-01-301 / OH-01-302 / OH-01-303 / OH-01-304, Cassette 84A - 84E)
  Electronic Transcript available, Release form Yes
- Walter Morris, Oct 17, 1980 (Cd OH-01-130 /OH-01-131, Cassette 85A)
  Transcript available Box 4; Index available
- Mary Mullahey, Apr 20, 1980 (Cd OH-01-132 / OH-01-133, Cassette 86A)
- T.J. Murphy, May 21, 1997 (Cd OH-01-383, Cassette 240A)
  Transcript available Box 4; Index available; Release form
- Al Nash, Apr 6, 1981 (Cd OH-01-362, Cassette 87A)
- Pauline Newman, Jan 19, 1980 (Cd OH-01-208, Cassette 227A - 227B)
- John Norman, undated (Cassette 202A)
- Thomas Noschese, Oct 1, 1980 (Cassette 88A, Cd OH-01-415 / OH-01-416 / OH-01-417)
- Frank Novich National Maritime Union, Apr 5, 1981 (Cd OH-01-350 / OH-01-351, Cassette 89A - 89C)
- William Nuchow, Aug 6, 1985 (Cd OH-01-355, Cassette 90A - 90B)
- Thomas O'Brien, Jul 11, 1984 (Cd OH-01-134, Cassette 33A)
- Ben Occhiogrosso, Jul 6, 1981 (Cd OH-01-135 / OH-01-136, Cassette 91A)
- Old Westbury, undated (Cassette 192A MISSING)
- John O'Neil, Jul 23, 1980 (Cassette 92A, Cd OH-01-418 / OH-01-419)